{
	"key": "cr1",
"answer": "app",
"shownQuestion": "What will you create?",
"parent": null,
"children": [
    {
        "key": "cr1q1",
        "answer": "job board",
        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
        "children": [
            {
                "key": "cr1q1p1",
                "answer": "lists",
                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                "children": [
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p1q1",
                        "answer": "Job name",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p1"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p1q2",
                        "answer": "short description",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p1"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p1q3",
                        "answer": "link to detailed page",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p1"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p1q4",
                        "answer": "money for the project",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p1"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p1q5",
                        "answer": "date posted",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p1"
                    }
                ],
                "parent": "cr1q1"
            },
            {
                "key": "cr1q1p2",
                "answer": "job-creation form",
                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                "children": [
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p2q1",
                        "answer": "purpose",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p2"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p2q2",
                        "answer": "descriptions",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p2"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p2q3",
                        "answer": "payment",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p2"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p2q4",
                        "answer": "visuals",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [
                            {
                                "key": "cr1q1p2q4p1",
                                "answer": "wireframe builder",
                                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                                "children": [],
                                "parent": "cr1q1p2q4"
                            }
                        ],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p2"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p2q5",
                        "answer": "preferred languages",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p2"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p2q6",
                        "answer": "type of job",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p2"
                    }
                ],
                "parent": "cr1q1"
            },
            {
                "key": "cr1q1p3",
                "answer": "description pages",
                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                "children": [
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p3q1",
                        "answer": "title",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p3"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p3q2",
                        "answer": "company/person contracting the work",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p3"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p3q3",
                        "answer": "languages wanted",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p3"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p3q4",
                        "answer": "wireframe mockup",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p3"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p3q5",
                        "answer": "user stories",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p3"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q1p3q6",
                        "answer": "money offered",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q1p3"
                    }
                ],
                "parent": "cr1q1"
            }
        ],
        "parent": "cr1"
    },
    {
        "key": "cr1q2",
        "answer": "educational",
        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
        "children": [
            {
                "key": "cr1q2p1",
                "answer": "blog",
                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                "children": [],
                "parent": "cr1q2"
            },
            {
                "key": "cr1q2p2",
                "answer": "reference articles",
                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                "children": [
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q2p2q1",
                        "answer": "teamwork",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q2p2"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q2p2q2",
                        "answer": "Git and Github",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [
                            {
                                "key": "cr1q2p2q2p1",
                                "answer": "how-to-fork article",
                                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                                "children": [],
                                "parent": "cr1q2p2q2"
                            },
                            {
                                "key": "cr1q2p2q2p2",
                                "answer": "writing good commit messages",
                                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                                "children": [],
                                "parent": "cr1q2p2q2"
                            }
                        ],
                        "parent": "cr1q2p2"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q2p2q3",
                        "answer": "languages",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [
                            {
                                "key": "cr1q2p2q3p1",
                                "answer": "javascript articles",
                                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                                "children": [],
                                "parent": "cr1q2p2q3"
                            },
                            {
                                "key": "cr1q2p2q3p2",
                                "answer": "Vue articles",
                                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                                "children": [],
                                "parent": "cr1q2p2q3"
                            },
                            {
                                "key": "cr1q2p2q3p3",
                                "answer": "React articles",
                                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                                "children": [],
                                "parent": "cr1q2p2q3"
                            },
                            {
                                "key": "cr1q2p2q3p4",
                                "answer": "node.js",
                                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                                "children": [],
                                "parent": "cr1q2p2q3"
                            },
                            {
                                "key": "cr1q2p2q3p5",
                                "answer": "python articles",
                                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                                "children": [],
                                "parent": "cr1q2p2q3"
                            }
                        ],
                        "parent": "cr1q2p2"
                    }
                ],
                "parent": "cr1q2"
            },
            {
                "key": "cr1q2p3",
                "answer": "boilerplate/example links",
                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                "children": [],
                "parent": "cr1q2"
            }
        ],
        "parent": "cr1"
    },
    {
        "key": "cr1q3",
        "answer": "community-focused",
        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
        "children": [
            {
                "key": "cr1q3p1",
                "answer": "forum",
                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                "children": [],
                "parent": "cr1q3"
            },
            {
                "key": "cr1q3p2",
                "answer": "team board (slack channels??)",
                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                "children": [],
                "parent": "cr1q3"
            },
            {
                "key": "cr1q3p3",
                "answer": "user profiles",
                "shownQuestion": "What structures need to be in place to guarantee this quality?",
                "children": [
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q3p3q1",
                        "answer": "messages",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q3p3"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q3p3q2",
                        "answer": "location",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q3p3"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q3p3q3",
                        "answer": "preferred languages",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q3p3"
                    },
                    {
                        "key": "cr1q3p3q4",
                        "answer": "Github link",
                        "shownQuestion": "What qualities will it have?",
                        "children": [],
                        "parent": "cr1q3p3"
                    }
                ],
                "parent": "cr1q3"
            }
        ],
        "parent": "cr1"
    }
]
}